How much time do we have to do something great?
tick, tick... BOOM! is a drama, music film directed by Lin-Manuel Miranda.
On the brink of turning 30, a promising theater composer navigates love, friendship
and the pressure to create something great before time runs out.
Jonathan Larson, played by Andrew Garfield.
Susan Wilson, played by Alexandra Shipp.
Michael, played by Robin de Jesús.
Carolyn, played by Michaela Jaé Rodriguez.
Freddy, played by Ben Levi Ross.
Ira Weitzman, played by Jonathan Marc Sherman.
Tick, Tick...
(also stylized as tick, tick...
BOOM!) is a 2021 American biographical  musical film directed by
Lin-Manuel Miranda in his feature directorial debut.
Written by Steven Levenson, who also serves as an executive producer, it is based on the stage musical of the same name by
Jonathan Larson, a semi-autobiographical story about Larson writing a musical to enter into the theater industry.
The film stars Andrew Garfield as Larson, alongside Robin de Jesús,
Alexandra Shipp, Joshua Henry, Judith Light, and Vanessa Hudgens.
Tick, Tick...
had its world premiere at the AFI Fest on November 10, 2021, and began a limited
theatrical release two days later, before streaming on Netflix on November 19.
The film received positive reviews for Garfield's
performance, the editing, and Miranda's direction.
It was named one of the best films of 2021 by the American Film Institute, and was nominated for Best Motion Picture - Musical or Comedy at the
79th Golden Globe Awards, Best Picture at the 27th Critics' Choice Awards, as well as Best Film Editing at the 94th Academy Awards.
For his performance, Garfield won the Golden Globe Award for Best Actor in a Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy, and was
nominated as Best Lead Actor for the Academy Award, Screen Actors Guild Award, and Critics' Choice Movie Award.
The film explores themes of new york city, composer,
artist, musical, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.